Welcome to Automatic School Bell System !

♦ This program helps you to play the school bell automatically according to the time table you selected. It can be adjust 
  easily to the user. Anyone can easily handle this program as it consist with an user-friendly interface. I hope this 
  program will be very useful for schools.

PC Requirments that needed to run the Automatic School Bell System Software ;

• Minimum screen resolution - 1024x768 (1280x768 or higher Recommended)
• Speakers
• Keyboard & Mouse
• Nothing else special :) 

**Important !!!
**Please note that you should have installed "VB6 extended runtime setup" that I've included in the redist
folder (Automatic School Bell\redist) before using the application. Otherwise this program shouldn't able to run.
**And also you have to install all the fonts in the folder named "fonts".(Automatic School Bell\Fonts)

©2015UApps Inc.
ulidutheerake@outlook.com
ulidutheerake@gmail.com
C.N : 0716183426
      0718371368